Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - F
        - Fat Joe - Get it poppin', 2005; SR-15137; Fat Joe; Nelly (Box 262)
          Catalog # PR 301707; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301707-A1
        - Fat Joe - Listen baby, 2005; SR-15138; Fat Joe; Mashonda (Box 262)
          Catalog # PR 301883; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301883-1
        - Fat Killahz - Get ya paper, 2005; SR-15139; Fat Killahz (Box 262)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # 9675-DINWER-1 (A)
          No Tyze Entertainment
        - Fat Larry's Band - Act like you know, 1982; SR-15140; Fat Larry's Band (Box 262)
          Catalog # AS 1402; A-side Matrix # AS 1402AS-1B
          WMOT Records
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Fat Larry's Band - Fascination; Center City, 1976; SR-15141; Fat Larry's Band (Box 262)
          Catalog # DSKO 82; A-side Matrix # ST-DSKO 32981-A
        - Fat Larry's Band - Sunrise, sunset, 1986; SR-15142; Fat Larry's Band (Box 263)
          Catalog # DMD 956; A-side Matrix # ST DM 49805-1
          Omni Records
        - Fatback - The girl is fine (So fine), 1983; SR-15143; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          Catalog # SP D 409 DJ; A-side Matrix # SP-D-409-82-NP-6196-PRC-C1-1-1
          Spring Records
        - Fatback Band - Keep on steppin', 1974; SR-15144; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          Catalog # SEW 001-A; A-side Matrix # DMC7328 A-1/4-89
          Southbound
        - Fatback Band - Raising hell, 1975; SR-15145; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          Catalog # EV-6905; A-side Matrix # EV6905A-AD
          Event Records Inc.
        - Fatback Band - Yum yum, 1975; SR-15146; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          Catalog # 2391-184 A; A-side Matrix # 2391184 A//1
          Polydor
        - Fatback Band - Fatbackin' (The Perception Sessions) (Disc one), 2000; SR-15147; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15148. Double album.
          Catalog # 44003; A-side Matrix # AE 51537/A
          Earmark
          Italy
        - Fatback Band - Fatbackin' (The Perception Sessions) (Disc two), 2000; SR-15148; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15147. Double album.
          Catalog # 44003; A-side Matrix # AE 51539/A
        - Fatback - Live, 1987; SR-15149; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          Catalog # STL 12; A-side Matrix # STL-12-A2
          Start Records
        - Fatback Band - With love, 1983; SR-15150; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          Catalog # SEW 024-A; A-side Matrix # DMD-2667 A-1/1-90 C
        - Fatback Band - I found lovin', 1983; SR-15151; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15152. Different discs.
          Catalog # 12 CHE 8401; A-side Matrix # 12CHE8401 A
          Master Mix
        - Walsh, Steve - I found loving; Na na hey hey kiss him goodbye, 1987; SR-15152; Walsh, Steve (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15151. Different discs.
          Catalog # 12 A1 299; A-side Matrix # 12-A-1299 A-1
          A.1. Records
        - Fatback - On the floor, 1982; SR-15153; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          Catalog # SP-1-6736; A-side Matrix # SP-1-6736BS HRM-1
        - Fatback Band - Yum yum (Gimme some), 1991; SR-15154; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          Catalog # DEBTX 3122; A-side Matrix # DEBTX 3122 A-1
          Debut
        - Fatback - Up against the wall, 1983; SR-15155; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15156. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SPR-12-412; A-side Matrix # SPR-12412-A 1729
        - Fatback - Up against the wall, 1983; SR-15156; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15155. 2 copies.
        - Fatback - Kool whip, 1981; SR-15157; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15157. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRO 166 DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-166-81NP-5558 PRC-C1-1-1
        - Fatback - Kool whip, 1981; SR-15158; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 263)
        - Fatback - On the floor, 1982; SR-15159; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          Catalog # PRO 184; A-side Matrix # PRO-184-A-82NP5889PRC-C1-1-1
        - Fatback - You're my candy sweet, 1979; SR-15160; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15161. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-D-402; A-side Matrix # SP-D-402-79NP-4364-S-K
        - Fatback - You're my candy sweet, 1979; SR-15161; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15160. 2 copies.
        - Fatback - Rockin' to the beat, 1981; SR-15162; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 263)
          Catalog # PRO 170 DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-170-81-NP-5761-PRC-C1-1-1
        - Fatboy Slim - Going out of my head, 1997; SR-15163; Fatboy Slim (Box 263)
          Catalog # SKINT 19; A-side Matrix # SKINT+19+AA
          Skint
          Brighton, United Kingdom
        - Fatboy Slim - The Rockafeller skank, 1988; SR-15164; Fatboy Slim (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15165. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SKINT 35; A-side Matrix # SKINT 35AA
        - Fatboy Slim - The Rockafeller skank, 1988; SR-15165; Fatboy Slim (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15164. 2 copies.
        - Fatboy Slim - Millenium jam (Live) (Disc one), 2000; SR-15166; Fatboy Slim (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15167. Double album.
          Catalog # FB-0121; A-side Matrix # FB-0121-A
          Fatboy Slim
        - Fatboy Slim - Millenium jam (Live) (Disc two), 2000; SR-15167; Fatboy Slim (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15166. Double album.
          Catalog # FB-0121; A-side Matrix # FB-0121-C
        - Fatboy Slim - Star 69 (What the f**k) (The remixes) (Disc one), 2001; SR-15168; Fatboy Slim (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15169. Double album. Annotated.
          Catalog # ASW38777-1; A-side Matrix # ASW38777 LP1-A
          Astralwerks
        - Fatboy Slim - Star 69 (What the f**k) (The remixes) (Disc two), 2001; SR-15169; Fatboy Slim (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15168. Double album. Annotated.
          Catalog # ASW38777-1; A-side Matrix # ASW38777 LP2-A
        - Fatboy Slim - Everybody needs a 303, 1997; SR-15170; Fatboy Slim (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15171. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SKINT 31; A-side Matrix # SKINT 31AA
        - Fatboy Slim - Everybody needs a 303, 1997; SR-15171; Fatboy Slim (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15170. 2 copies.
        - Fatboy Slim - Everybody needs a 303, 1995; SR-15172; Fatboy Slim (Box 263)
          Catalog # SKINT 6; A-side Matrix # SKINT+6+A
        - Fatboy Slim - Better living through chemistry, 1996; SR-15173; Fatboy Slim (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15174. Different discs.
          Catalog # BRASSIC 2LP; A-side Matrix # BRASSIC 2 LP-A1
        - Midfield General - Stigs in love, 1996; SR-15174; Midfield General (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15173. Different discs.
          Catalog # SKINT 10; A-side Matrix # SKINT-10-AA
        - F.A.T.E. - Just because, 1999; SR-15175; F.A.T.E. (Box 263)
          Catalog # PRO-A-9977; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-9977-SR11
        - F.A.T.E. - Just because, 1999; SR-15176; F.A.T.E. (Box 263)
          Catalog # PRO-A-99-77-A; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-9977-SR11
        - Father Dom - Rumors, 1995; SR-15177; Father Dom (Box 263)
          Catalog # JDAB-42316-1; A-side Matrix # JDAB-42316-1-C1
          Jive
        - Father Father - Father father, 1991; SR-15178; Father Father (Box 263)
          Catalog # GODX 52; A-side Matrix # GODX 52 A-2J-1-1
          Go! Discs
        - Father - World wide; Give me love, 1997; SR-15180; Father (Box 263)
          Catalog # SPRO 30193; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30193-A
          Luke Records
        - Father MC - Treat them like they want to be treated, 1990; SR-15181; Father MC (Box 263)
          Catalog # MCA-24024; A-side Matrix # MCA-9901-SS2
          Uptown Records
        - Father MC - Hey, how ya doin, 1995; SR-15182; Father MC (Box 263)
          Catalog # 12 MISH 7; A-side Matrix # 12 MISH 7 A
          Moja
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - Fatman Scoop - Ayo, 2004; SR-15183; Fatman Scoop; Crooklyn Clan (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15184. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AV300; A-side Matrix # AV-300-A-RE
          AV8
        - Fatman Scoop - Ayo, 2004; SR-15184; Fatman Scoop; Crooklyn Clan (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15183. 2 copies.
        - Fatman Scoop - Hands up…now get your hands up, 1997; SR-15185; Fatman Scoop; Crooklyn Clan (Box 263)
          Catalog # AV42; A-side Matrix # AV-42 A RE-2
        - Fats Comet - Dee jay's dream, 1985; SR-15186; Fats Comet (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15187. 2 copies.
          Catalog # WR004A; A-side Matrix # WR 004-A-1
          World Records
        - Fats Comet - Dee jay's dream, 1985; SR-15187; Fats Comet (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15186. 2 copies.
        - Fats Comet - Stormy weather, 1986; SR-15188; Fats Comet (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15189. 2 copies.
          Catalog # LR 1001-DJ; A-side Matrix # LR 1001 A
          Logarhythm
        - Fats Comet - Stormy weather, 1986; SR-15189; Fats Comet (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15188. 2 copies.
        - Fatt Dex - Creepin', 2001; SR-15190; Fatt Dex; Trey (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15191. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 671390.6; A-side Matrix # 671390-6 A-1
          Sony Dance
          Australia
        - Fatt Dex - Creepin', 2001; SR-15191; Fatt Dex; Trey (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15190. 2 copies.
        - Fattahi, Dariush - Hacker, 1997; SR-15192; Fattahi, Dariush (Box 263)
          Catalog # PRG7091; A-side Matrix # PRG 7091 A
          PRG (Progressive Motion Records)
        - Big Rap & Luciano - Balas perdidas; Rap da Algeria, 1995; SR-15193; Big Rap & Luciano; Bidy & White (Box 263)
          Catalog # 443.054; A-side Matrix # 446054 A
          Afegan
          Brazil
        - Fawaz, Sheik - Mohamed's house, 1988; SR-15194; Fawaz, Sheik (Box 263)
          Catalog # YRT 10-A; A-side Matrix # YRT 10 A-1U-1-1
          Circa Records
        - Fax Yourself - Sunshine; I feel love, 1990; SR-15195; Fax Yourself (Box 263)
          Catalog # SSL12-1-A; A-side Matrix # C-35306
          Sandstone Music
          Chatsworth, California
        - Faxe - Time for changes, 1983; SR-15196; Faxe (Box 263)
          Catalog # MEMIX 006; A-side Matrix #
          Memory Records
        - Faye, Alma - It's over, 1979; SR-15197; Faye, Alma (Box 263)
          Catalog # NBD 20158 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBD-20158-AS
          Casablanca
        - Faze Action - Moving cities, 1999; SR-15198; Faze Action (Box 263)
          Catalog # PRO A 9985 A; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-9985-A10-44781-A-SR1
          F-111 Records
        - Faze One - Layin' down a beat, 1986; SR-15199; Faze One (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15200. 2 copies.
          Catalog # UKHAN 1; A-side Matrix # UKHAN-1-A1
          Streetwave
        - Faze One - Layin' down a beat, 1986; SR-15200; Faze One (Box 263)
          In same jacket as # SR-15199. 2 copies.
        - Faze One - Layin' down a beat, 1986; SR-15201; Faze One (Box 263)
          Catalog # SUD 056; A-side Matrix # SUD-056-A
        - Fearless - Creepin' up on ya, 1994; SR-15203; Fearless; Fearless Four (Box 264)
          Catalog # 12-PO242; A-side Matrix # 12-PO-242-A
          Wrap Records
        - Fearless - Creepin' up on ya, 1994; SR-15204; Fearless; Fearless Four (Box 264)
        - Fearless Four - Rockin' it, 1982; SR-15205; Fearless Four (Box 264)
          Catalog # ER-6028; A-side Matrix # EV1150-BX
          Enjoy Records
        - Fearless Four - Just rock, 1983; SR-15206; Fearless Four (Box 264)
          Catalog # ED 4900; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-0-67924-A-2
        - Fearon, Phil - Ain't nothing but a house party, 1986; SR-15207; Fearon, Phil (Box 264)
          Catalog # 4V9 43096; A-side Matrix # 4V9 43096 BS ES1
        - Phil Fearon & Galaxy - What do I do (Carnival mix), 1984; SR-15208; Phil Fearon & Galaxy (Box 264)
          Annotated. Different jacket
          Catalog # XENY 510; A-side Matrix # 12 ENY 510 A-1U-1-1
          Ensign
        - Federation - Donkey; What if I had a gun, 2004; SR-15209; Federation (Box 264)
          Catalog # 7087 6 18644 1 0; A-side Matrix # 07087-618644-1-0-A
          Virgin
        - Feel - I'd like to, 1982; SR-15210; Feel (Box 264)
          Catalog # SUD 011; A-side Matrix # SUD-011-A
        - Fehlfarben - Glut und asche, 1983; SR-15211; Fehlfarben (Box 264)
          Catalog # 1C 064-46 715; A-side Matrix # 46715-A1
          Welt-Rekord
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Music of many colours, 1986; SR-15212; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Ayers, Roy; Fela (Box 264)
          Catalog # CELL 6125; A-side Matrix # CELL-6125-A
          Celluloid
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Live in Amsterdam (Disc one), 1984; SR-15213; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Fela (Box 264)
          In same jacket as # SR-15214. Double album.
          Catalog # 2401293; A-side Matrix # M6 240129 3 A 21
          EMI
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Live in Amsterdam (Disc two), 1984; SR-15214; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Fela (Box 264)
          In same jacket as # SR-15213. Double album.
          Catalog # 2401303; A-side Matrix # 240130 3 A21
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - No agreement, 1985; SR-15215; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Fela (Box 264)
          Catalog # CELL 6122; A-side Matrix # CELL-6122-THIS
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Army arrangement, 1985; SR-15216; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Fela (Box 264)
          Catalog # CELL 6115; A-side Matrix # CELL-6115-THIS
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Teacher don't teach me nonsense, 1986; SR-15217; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Fela (Box 264)
          Catalog # 885 452-1; A-side Matrix # 222 885 4521 A POLYGRAM
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Fela Anikulapo Kuti and the Africa 70 (Disc one), 1973; SR-15218; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Africa 70; Fela (Box 264)
          In same jacket as # SR-15219. Double album.
          Catalog # EDP 1547201A; A-side Matrix # EDP 1547201 A-1-1-1-1
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Fela Anikulapo Kuti and the Africa 70 (Disc two), 1971; SR-15219; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Africa 70; Fela (Box 264)
          In same jacket as # SR-15218. Double album.
          Catalog # EDP 1547211; A-side Matrix # EDP 1547211 A-1-1-1-1
        - Kuti, Fela Ransome - Live!, 1971; SR-15220; Kuti, Fela Ransome; Africa 70; Baker, Ginger; Fela (Box 264)
          Two different jackets
          Catalog # 1A 038-04933; A-side Matrix # 5C-038-04933-A-35859-1-1
          Netherlands
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - No agreement, 1985; SR-15221; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Fela (Box 264)
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Shuffering and shmiling, 1985; SR-15222; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Fela (Box 264)
          Catalog # CELL 6117; A-side Matrix # CELL-6117-THIS
        - Kuti, Fela Ransome - The '69 Los Angeles sessions, 1993; SR-15223; Kuti, Fela Ransome; Nigeria 70; Fela (Box 264)
          Catalog # STERNS 3005; A-side Matrix # STERNS 3005 A
          Stern's Music
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Zombie, 1976; SR-15224; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Afrika 70 (Box 264)
          Catalog # 829 684-1; A-side Matrix # 222 829684 1 // 2 380 POLYGRAPH
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Black man's cry (Disc one), 1987; SR-15225; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Fela (Box 264)
          In same jacket as # SR-15226. Double album.
          Catalog # 835 200-1; A-side Matrix # 835199-1 A
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Black man's cry (Disc two), 1987; SR-15226; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Fela (Box 264)
          In same jacket as # SR-15225. Double album.
          Catalog # 835 201-1; A-side Matrix # 835199-1 C
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Zombie, 1985; SR-15227; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Afrika 70; Fela (Box 264)
          Catalog # CELL 6116; A-side Matrix # CELL-6116-A
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Mr. Follow Follow, 1975; SR-15228; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Africa 70; Fela (Box 264)
          Catalog # CELL 6124; A-side Matrix # CELL-6124-THIS SIDE
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Live in Amsterdam (Disc one), 1984; SR-15229; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Fela (Box 264)
          In same jacket as # SR-15230. Double album.
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Live in Amsterdam (Disc two), 1984; SR-15230; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Fela (Box 264)
          In same jacket as # SR-15229. Double album.
          Catalog # 2401303; A-side Matrix # M6 346078 2
        - Kuti, Fela Ransome - Shakara, 1972; SR-15231; Kuti, Fela Ransome; Africa 70; Fela (Box 264)
          In same jacket as # SR-15232. 2 copies. Distributed by African Record Centre, Brooklyn
          Catalog # EM23.05; A-side Matrix # EMI LP 008NA-F6S
        - Kuti, Fela Ransome - Shakara, 1972; SR-15232; Kuti, Fela Ransome; Africa 70; Fela (Box 264)
          In same jacket as # SR-15231. 2 copies. Distributed by African Record Centre, Brooklyn
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Unknown soldier, 1981; SR-15233; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Fela (Box 264)
          Catalog # UM 0002; A-side Matrix # UM-0002-A
          Uno Melodic Records
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Coffin for Head of State, 1981; SR-15234; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Fela (Box 264)
          Reissue, yr. ca. 2001?
          Catalog # KALP 003; A-side Matrix # M6 342666 2
          Kalakuta Records
          Nigeria
        - Kuti, Fela Ransome - He miss road, 1975; SR-15235; Kuti, Fela Ransome; Africa 70; Fela (Box 264)
          Reissue, Barclay france 2001
          Catalog # 549 652-1; A-side Matrix # 5496521 A
        - Kuti, Fela Ransome - Open & close, 1975; SR-15236; Kuti, Fela Ransome; Africa 70; Fela (Box 264)
          Catalog # 2C 068-81.957; A-side Matrix # 81957 A 21
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Original sufferhead, 1981; SR-15237; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Fela (Box 264)
          Catalog # SPART 1177; A-side Matrix # SPART-1177 A//1
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - No agreement, 1977; SR-15238; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Fela (Box 264)
          Catalog # 829 682-1; A-side Matrix # 222 829682 1 // 1 380 POLYGRAPH
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Beasts of no nation, 1989; SR-15239; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Egypt 80; Fela (Box 264)
          Catalog # JD-EUR 360153; A-side Matrix # 360 153 A
          Eurobond Records
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Ikoyi blindness, 1976; SR-15240; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Africa 70; Fela (Box 264)
          Reissue, 2001 Barclay france
          Catalog # 549 238-1; A-side Matrix # 5492381 A
        - Kuti, Fela Ransome - Alagbon close, 1975; SR-15241; Kuti, Fela Ransome; Fela (Box 264)
          In same jacket as # SR-15242. 2 copies. Distributed by African Record Centre, Brooklyn
          Catalog # EM2313A; A-side Matrix # EM2313A
          Editions Makossa
        - Kuti, Fela Ransome - Alagbon close, 1975; SR-15242; Kuti, Fela Ransome; Fela (Box 264)
          In same jacket as # SR-15241. 2 copies. Distributed by African Record Centre, Brooklyn
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Unnecessary begging, 1982; SR-15243; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Africa 70; Fela (Box 264)
          Distributed by African Record Centre, Brooklyn
          Catalog # M 2382; A-side Matrix # M-2382-A
          Makossa International Records
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Fear not for man, 1977; SR-15244; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Africa 70; Fela (Box 264)
          Catalog # 549 658-1; A-side Matrix # 549658 A
        - Kuti, Fela Anikulapo - Shuffering and shmiling, 1978; SR-15245; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Africa 70; Fela (Box 264)
          Catalog # 829 710-1; A-side Matrix # 222 829710 1 // 1 380 POLYGRAPH
        - Feldman - Wally boule noire, 1984; SR-15246; Feldman (Box 264)
          In same jacket as # SR-15247. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 817 879-1; A-side Matrix # 222 817 87 91 A
        - Feldman - Wally boule noire, 1984; SR-15247; Feldman (Box 264)
          In same jacket as # SR-15246. 2 copies.
        - Feliciano, Jose - Tu inmenso amor, 1987; SR-15248; Feliciano, Jose (Box 264)
          Catalog # 1C 064-7 90068 1 A; A-side Matrix # 7900681-A1
        - Felix & Jarvis - Jam the house, 1983; SR-15249; Felix & Jarvis (Box 264)
          Catalog # QUS 054; A-side Matrix # QUS-054-A
        - Feliciano, Jose - Cheo, 1971; SR-15250; Feliciano, Jose (Box 264)
          Catalog # Vaya records V-5; A-side Matrix # V5 5-A
          Vaya Records
        - Felli & Buddy - The exploding fist, 1998; SR-15251; Felli & Buddy (Box 264)
          Catalog # CF 2839; A-side Matrix # CF-2839-A
          Caffeine Records
          Massapequa Park, New York
        - Felt - The pictorial Jackson review, 1988; SR-15252; Felt (Box 264)
          Catalog # 88561-8234-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-8234-1-A
        - Felony - Felony's butter, 1996; SR-15253; Felony (Box 264)
          Catalog # SPRO-11601; A-side Matrix # SPRO-7087-6-11601-1-6-A
        - Female Body Inspectors - The girl pulled a dog, 1986; SR-15254; Female Body Inspectors (Box 264)
          Catalog # 0-20580; A-side Matrix # 0-20580-A-SH1
        - Femme Fatale - 1999, 1999; SR-15255; Femme Fatale (Box 264)
          Catalog # rprolp 0972; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0972 A
        - Fenderella - A wild and crazzy song; Funk's gone crazy, 1980; SR-15256; Fenderella (Box 264)
          Catalog # 448; A-side Matrix # TKD-448-A-AM
          T.K. Disco
          Hialeah, Florida
        - Ferguson, Maynard - Rocky II disco, 1979; SR-15257; Ferguson, Maynard (Box 265)
          Catalog # 43-11039; A-side Matrix # XSS-165961-1C
          Columbia
        - Ferrante & Teicher - Piano portraits, 1976; SR-15258; Ferrante & Teicher (Box 265)
          Catalog # UA-LA585-G; A-side Matrix # UA-585-1
        - Ferrara - I gave my heart to the Pacman, 1982; SR-15259; Ferrara; Hoo, Sally (Box 265)
          Catalog # JBF-8080-A; A-side Matrix # JBF 8080A
          Revolver Records
        - Ferrara - Shake it baby love; Love attack, 1979; SR-15260; Ferrara (Box 264)
          Catalog # MD 509; A-side Matrix # MD-509AS-1B
          Midsong International
        - Ferrari - Let your mind be free, 1982; SR-15261; Ferrari (Box 265)
          Catalog # SH-573; A-side Matrix # VID-223-A
        - Ferry, Bryan - Limbo, 1987; SR-15262; Ferry, Bryan (Box 265)
          Catalog # 0-20846; A-side Matrix # 0-20846-A-SH1
          Reprise Records
        - Ferry, Bryan - Kiss and tell, 1987; SR-15263; Ferry, Bryan (Box 265)
          Catalog # 0-20841; A-side Matrix # 0-20841-A-SH1
        - Fetchin Bones - Super freak; Jesse James, 1988; SR-15264; Fetchin Bones (Box 265)
          Catalog # SPRO-79287; A-side Matrix # SPRO-1-79289-101111
          Capitol Records
        - Fettes Brot - Da draussen, 2000; SR-15265; Fettes Brot (Box 265)
          Catalog # YPS 7029-0; A-side Matrix # FB DD 1 A
          Yo Mama's Recording
          Hamburg, Germany
        - Feva, Sandra - Sexyonic, 1989; SR-15266; Feva, Sandra (Box 265)
          Catalog # 12-318; A-side Matrix # GRANDSTAND 12-318 A
          Grandstand Records
        - Fever - Fever, 1979; SR-15267; Fever (Box 265)
          Catalog # F-9580; A-side Matrix # F-9580-A
          Fantasy
        - Fever - Way to go, 1990; SR-15268; Fever (Box 265)
          Catalog # TB 958; A-side Matrix # TB-958 A-RE 1-1
          Tommy Boy
        - Fever & Chase - Come on give me what I need, SR-15269; Fever & Chase (Box 265)
          Catalog # TROP 004; A-side Matrix # TROP-004 A
          Tropicana Records
        - Fiasco, Lupe - Kick push; Just might be okay, 2006; SR-15270; Fiasco, Lupe (Box 265)
          Catalog # PR 302173; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-302173B-1 A
        - Fiasco, Lupe - I gotcha, 2006; SR-15271; Fiasco, Lupe (Box 265)
          Catalog # PR 302299; A-side Matrix # ST-A-94408/302299A-1
        - Fiasco, Lupe - I gotcha, 2006; SR-15272; Fiasco, Lupe (Box 265)